Guide to the T. W. Anderson Papers SC0911
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-093
  - Correspondence
    - Mentz, Raul P. - and Durbin, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Mentz, Raul P. -modelling, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Raul Mentz - papers, reports… etc, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Mentz, Raul P. - tech. report paper, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Mentz, Raul P. - tech. report on inversion, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Miller, John, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Dr. Kenneth S., 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Miller, William F., 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mitchell, Bridger, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Mohan, Dr. Lakshmi, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Moon, 1992 Aug 19 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Morimune, Kimio, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Morimune SAWA correspondence, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Morimune SAWA correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Morimune SAWA correspondence, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Mosteller, Frederick, 1976-1984 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Muirhead Roff Adelaide, 1970-1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Muth, 1979 Jul 16 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - McDonald, James B. (paper with Dean S. Dutton), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Nerlov, Professor Marc, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Nerlove, Marc, 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Neyman, Jerzey, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Nicholson, George E., Jr., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Nold, Frederick C., 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Nold, Frederick C. -proposals, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Nold, Frederick C. -proposals, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1970-1981 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Olkin, Ingram, 1973-1990 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Onicescu, Octav (Professor), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Q - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Quandt, Richard E., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - R - miscellaneous, 1976-1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - R misc (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Ramsey, James, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - RAO, C. R., 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ray, Dr. Gordon N., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Reunsel, Gregory, 1971-1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Resnick, Sidney I., 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Revankar, Nagesh (Professor), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Richardson, David H., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Rickart, Charles E., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Rizvi, M. Haseeb, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Robbins, Herbert, 1973-1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Robison, Roy J., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Rohr, Robert J., 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Roy, S. N. Memorial volume, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Rubin, Ernest, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Rubin, Herman, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1976-1983 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Samuels, Professor Stephen M. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Sanderson, Warren, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Sarhan, A., E., 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Satlow, Frank P., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Misc. rev., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Savage, I. Richard, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - SAWA, Professor Takamitsu, 1972-1982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - SAWA bibliography biography dittos (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - SAWA, TAKAMITSU - key parameter values, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - SAWA-Mariano monograph, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Sclove corresp, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Sclove, Stanley L. - correspondence, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Sclove, Stanley L. - correspondence, 1967-1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Sclove corresp, 1976-1977 Apr (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Sclove Anderson correspondence, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Sclove, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Sclove Anderson correspondence, 1973-1974 Aug (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Sclove Anderson correspondence, 1973 Jul - Oct (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Sclove Anderson correspondence, 1973 Feb - Jul (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Sclove Anderson correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Sclove Anderson: solution manual correspondence (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Sclove, Professor Stanley text on statistics for social scientists, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Segerdahl, Carl-otto Skandinavisk aktuarie tidskrift, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Ash Sen Gupta, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Sen Gupta, Ashis, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Sengupta Sinha (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Shannon, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Paul Shannon, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Shaman, Paul - correspondence, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Shaman, Paul, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Shaman, Paul - correspondence, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Shaman, Paul - correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Paul Shaman - personal data (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Shami, Professor Charles H., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Shoemaker, Professor E. M. (Simon Fraser University), 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SHYE, Samuel, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gary Simon, 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Nozer Singpurwalla, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Smith, K. J. C. (Mr.) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Solomon, Herbert, 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Somers, Robert (Professor), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Spicer… AAS lifetime mentor award nomination, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Srivastava - assessment of, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Francois E. Steffens, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Stein, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Stuart, Alan, 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Styan, Mr. George, 1969-1989 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Styan, George - appointment, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Sugiyama, Takakazu (V. A. Edgeloe), 1970-1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Suppes, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Switzer (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - A. Takemura - cur. Vitae, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Takeuchi, Kei, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Taylor, John, 1973-1984 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Martha Thomas, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - T K R, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Tintner, Gerhard, 1972-1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Tomaszewicz, A. S. (Dr.), 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Trumbo, B. E., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - U - Miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Ushakov, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Venkataraman, Lakshmi, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - W Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Wahba, Grace, 1970-1976 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Watson, Geoffrey S., 1982 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - C2 Wei, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Wichura, Michael, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Wilburn, Arthur J., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Williams, James S., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Wilson, Dr. O. Meredith, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Wishart, D. M. G., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Herman Wold (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Herman Wold, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Wold, Professor Herman, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Wolfowitz, Professor J., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous, 1978-1990 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Young, D. L. (Professor) (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - ZARE, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Zurbenko, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wold papers, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Research paper, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Vinod, 1998 Dec (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Percentage Points, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - TR (my correction to Yasow), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Yasoo Amemiya Testing dimensiality, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Yasua Amemiya Testing dimensionality, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Shama, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - TSA, instructor's manual, Shama, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Kai Tai's res proposal, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - from Baiyu Zhou (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Hendry, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Stuat Obit (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Navto, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Stuart Luberman, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Teaching Files
    - Anderson, T. W. (bibliography), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, T. W. (biographical sketch) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Letters, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - T. W. Anderson -invited lectures, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - T. W. Anderson - Leave of Absence, 1966-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - T. W. Anderson - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - T. W. Anderson - travel expenses, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - T. W. Anderson - visa information, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - T. W. Anderson (social sciences) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - To do, follow up, 1998 Mar-May (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cartons shipped (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - list of paper (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - goody, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Auals, 2001-2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Coint II Teds Report, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Econ ementi (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Origine, 2004 Dec 12 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Third Edition (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Irvene HAS, 1997 Feb 7-8 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Portugal, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Israel, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Isreal, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Isreael (office), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Seattle, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Fort Lauderdale, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Chicago, 1998 Sep 4-5 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Theo-Greece, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hiltu; clobalozabu (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Hilton (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - unlabeled (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Election of Foreign Associates, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - TNG for Central and South America Conference call, 2002 Sep 6 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - TNG for Central and South America Conference Call, 2003 Jul 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - photos (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - STAT seminar, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Econ seminar, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - MA sem, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Maih institute, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - STAT viore: self assessment (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - ASA championship, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - NSF statistics proposal, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - NSF funding request, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - NSF final report, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - NSF funding request, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - NSF Newlon, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - NSF (econ) proposal, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - NSF econ proposal, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Econ teaching food, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Stat Sam, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Statistics seminars, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Faculty salaries, 1973-1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Hotelling talk, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - My scholarly work, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Faculty, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Lauritzen, 1973 Oct (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Statistics sem., 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Foundations sem. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - IMS committee on named lecture, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - NSF proposal evaluations, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Dan, 1986 Oct - Nov (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Sheit, Sabbatical, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - fellowships, etc (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - fellowships, etc, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Lap+ Davis fellowship trust, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - NRC associates program (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - MA. Second ed. Donees. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - NSF, 1986 Jun (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - NSF: Trumbo, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - NSF progress report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - NSF proposal, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - NSF grant, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - NSF final project report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - NSF supplemental, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - NSF proposal, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - NSF proposal evaluations, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - NSF final report, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - NSF proposal, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - NSF, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - NSF final report, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - NSF, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - NSF funding, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Academic Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Steering Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Statistics Dept., 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - University Activities, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Statistics Dept., 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Statistics admissions, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Univ. activities, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Oral exams, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Oral questions, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Class lists (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Quals, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Quals, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Quals, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Stat orals, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Grad., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Stat quals, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - "ONR" proposal, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - ONR final report, 1981 Jul (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - ONR proposal, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - ONR annual report, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - ONR T.R.'s (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Econ dept. confidential, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Refereeing, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Miller (Provost), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - University, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - My university activities, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Report, 1974-1980 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Books to Buy, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Anderson Bibliography no. of reprints (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - My Bibliographical sketch, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - TSA: Intl. manual, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - To Receive reprints (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - CASBS, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Center, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - fellowships, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Leave of Absence, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Travel (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Misc. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Annual Faculty Report, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Annual Faculty Report, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - My finances, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Qual exam, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Qualifying misc exam, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Harry Paarsch, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - John Taylor, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - unlabeled (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - HSIAO, 1965-1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Mentz: summary + survey, 1971 Sep (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Mentz-inversion, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Mentz's paper, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - unlabeled (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Styan, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Discriminant function, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Miveo, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Econ, comm, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Switz, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Green Comm., 1971 Nov (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Olshen, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - IMS comm. On gifts + requests, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Faculty, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Academic, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - DOD Research, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - SWOPSI, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Cover, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - On economists, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Search committee, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Seminar Committee (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Privacy, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Teaching - lecture notes, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lecture notes, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 343A final exam, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 343A misc, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Stat 343B final exam, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 343B misc, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Stat 343 handouts I, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Stat 343 handouts II, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Stat 343 lectures 1-20, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Stat 343 lecture 21-25, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Stat 343 final exam, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Stat 343 solutions to final, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Stat 324 lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Stat 324 misc, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Stat 324 final exam, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Stat 324, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - TSA exam, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - TSA exam, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Stat 206 misc, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Stat 206, copy of lec notes, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Stat 206 evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Stat 206 questionaire, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Stat 206 misc, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Stat 206 simple regr., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Stat 206 multiple regr., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Stat 206 reading, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Stat 206 pre., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Stat 206 FA printouts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Stat 206 handouts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Stat 206 handouts to May 11, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Stat 206 lecture 1-15, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - stat 206 lecture 16-27, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Stat 206 lecture 21-26 F. A., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Stat 206 midterm, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Stat 206, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Econ 273 typed notes, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - econ 273, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Stat 207 TSA, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - TSA exam, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - unlabeled (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - TSA (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Research Files
    - unlabeled (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - OLKIN, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Fang Theorem, 1983 Oct (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - A Fary Annual Report, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - A Fang to Annals (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - A + Fary: cochairs TH, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lary + Chen, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - unlabeled (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Files for Sydney (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - On the theory of multivariate elliphically, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - On the Theory of Multivariate contumes distribution, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - FANG (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - MA(q) lecture: copy of jots (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Fang II, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Fancy + Math Review, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Fancy + Xu, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Fang paper + jrssb, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Fang + Dekker, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Corhans Th. W. Fang correspondence on paper (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Corhans, Th. Notes, 1986 May (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Fang, 1984-1986 Jul (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Fang + Zhang, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Fang: MLE's, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Revision: sample pages (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Delusthations (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Dust jacket, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Assistants (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Hsn + Knosles, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Permission: requests (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Deana Cisek, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Typing: Pat Strus, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Wiley: authors question (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Crustal Abundance, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Nozer, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Nozer, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Nozer, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Hrn: summer, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Hsu, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Huang Hsu: dissertation (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Leon Seltzer, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Holelling T2 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Hotelling's Canon-lowd (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Prudine, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Eynon (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Sclove (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - A-S Permission to copy (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Shube: encyclopedia, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Proofreading and Indexing instructions (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Tables, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Tables for manova, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Tables: Krishruiah (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Tables: pillar (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Tables: Davis, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - tables: biometrika (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Christina (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Solution (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Amemija, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Huzii, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Professor Anderson, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - RA fither Engine by Stanford, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - R. H. Fisher lecture ART (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - A Condition for Cointequation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Pine (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Printing, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Intunel, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - TR paper on components (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Word processor, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - photos of U of Athens Germany, 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - unlabeled, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Springer (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Ron B, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - unlabeled, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - 2 anan, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Monti, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - unlabeled, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Ms, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - unlabeled, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - unlabeled, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - netscape, 1987-1993 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - HSU, P. L. (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - unlabeled (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - notes (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - LAU, professor Lawrence J., 1975 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Misch (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Coper (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Roersa (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Farkas, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - MA e-book, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Table of Contents, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Frieman, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Ibergoam (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bn(1) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bn(2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - y=3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - B-P, 1965 May (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Binomial-poisson, 1963 Apr-Jun (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Binomial-poisson, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Binomial-poisson (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence to file (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - to sort out (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Durbin KSS (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Original technical report 25, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - panels + TSA: correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Panels + tsa PFL, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Panels + TSA: Goodman, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Panels + TSA Persi's copy, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Panel + TSA: early PPL, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Panels + TSA preliminary version, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Panels + TSA 2nd paper (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Repeated measure on AR TR 25, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Repeated measurements on AR: talk (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - TR no25 JASA, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Lazarsfeld letter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Robinson paper (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - MENT2 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - reprints (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - reprints (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - unlabeled (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Burnstein, Herman (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Student volume 3 number 2 incorporating data statistics, 1999 Nov (Box 21, Folder 5)